evilshare.com 2011-05-20

# EvilShare Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. By default, EvilShare does not collect or share personal information. This policy does not apply to information about you collected by our affiliated providers or third party Web sites and offerings linked to or otherwise accessible from EvilShare. The information collected or received by our affiliated providers and these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies. The following outlines our privacy policy. 

## Information Not Collected

When you access EvilShare (or any Web site), your web browser automatically sends information about your computer, e.g. your User agent and IP address. Because this information could be used to link you to your searches, we do not log (store) it at all. Another way that your searches are often tied together at other search engines are through browser cookies, Cookies are pieces of information that sit on your computer and get sent to the search engine on each request. At EvilShare, no cookies are used by default. 

## Information Collected

EvilShare may use advertising network providers to help present advertisements on EvilShare. These advertising networks may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer in order to provide targeted advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you while visiting other Web sites. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies. You can find out more about ad network providers and the choices you have about these technologies by clicking here. 

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on EvilShare.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to EvilShare.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

## Feedback

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us by going to the following link: [Contact](http://evilshare.com/contact)

## Changes to this Privacy Policy and Additional Information

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically. If there are significant changes to EvilShare's information practices, you will be provided with appropriate online notice. You may be provided other privacy-related information in connection with your use of offerings from EvilShare, as well as for special features and services not described in this Policy that may be introduced in the future.

Last Updated: 24 Nov 2010.
